DELUSION
So how has this caught fire?
Um, not sure. It's not
the right time for forest fires.
Not this time of the year.
It's much more likely that it was arson.
You see here? The ground's damp.
Hmm.
Inspector, something here.
Come on through.
The victim's teeth were also taken out.
Cases like this
have happened in other provinces.
And in every case,
teeth were missing from the bodies.
Forensics.
We found skeletal remains
near this large tree wrapped in cloth.
- Copy, over.
- Copy that.
- What's up, Wan?
- Wat.
I've got Dad with me.
Can I take him to stay at your place?
Uh-- What? Hang on. What happened?
We can't leave Dad with Mom anymore.
Sis, calm down. Tell me what happened.
I think Mom killed Uncle Sak.
Doctor, the next patient's here.
Shall I send her in?
Just give me a second, okay?
Sure.
Okay. Just stay calm.
Don't take Dad too far away yet.
An unfamiliar environment
might make him delirious.
Just find a place you can stay nearby.
I'll be there as soon as I can, okay, sis?
Just take it easy there.
Okay. I'll go to the lake house.
Come soon, Wat.
You again.
A fire broke out on your property.
Did you know that?
Did it?
If I'd known, I would have put it out.
Listen to me.
Human remains
have been found on your land.
You can't just keep saying
you don't know anything.
Remains?
Okay.
The hut that burned down
and the human remains
were both found on your land.
As of now,
your entire family are suspects.
You all need to come the station.
Where have your husband and kids gone?
I don't know.
They've left me here alone.
Come on, Nee.
INSPECTOR SASIDIT
CALL ENDED
There was a corpse in your backyard.
You're saying you have no idea.
It's big.
Someone could have got lost
or dumped a body there.
How would I know?
No one goes in there these days.
What about this tin full of teeth?
Can you explain how that got there?
These are all the cases
from the last 20 years
that I think are connected.
In the first ten years,
the victims were all found
within the same province.
MYSTERIOUS SKELETON DISCOVERED
And the ten years after that,
bodies with missing teeth were found
across multiple provinces.
POLICE TO SOLVE
MISSING PERSONS CASES
All before Mued and Sak.
And our main suspect?
There is no record of him moving.
Are you sure they're connected?
I'm sure the person we're looking for
committed all of these murders.
Well, if you need a warrant,
then just let me know.
Get this wrapped up.
The news is already spreading.
That's Mom's car. Is she meeting us here?
Aim! Just stay here.
I'll go talk to your mom first.
I'll bring her out to see you.
I miss Mom.
Aim, don't. Stop!
Stay here until I get back, understand?
If you disobey…
you won't see your mom again.
What's that?
Ah.
- You piece of shit.
- Ah!
You think?
Your family's money was made
with my family name too, you know?
Without my father's help,
would you have even
got those plots of land
to squeeze your money out of?
That family name you have…
it's hardly worth a thing.
And all…
you ever wanted from me
is my family's money.
You piece of fucking trash!
Fucking leech!
You fucked her right here, yeah?
You make me sick.
So what, huh?
You're gonna expose me?
You wanna ruin me, huh?
Don't you love your son?
Don't you love Aim?
Do you want to humiliate him?
Do you really think I'm that fucked up?
I would never do that.
But you're right about one thing.
It's always been about the money.
But it didn't come for free.
I traded my life…
I traded all my dignity, so…
I'm taking what I earned.
Have your divorce…
but Aim comes with me.
Your family
can't raise a decent human.
Just look at you.
That's…
Enough!
You fucking leech!
Please, Dad! No! No.
Aim!
Aunt Pannee.
If you don't come clean,
you'll be tried as an accomplice
and go to jail.
WANRUDEE
Hello?
Please. Please help.
Dad took my son away again.
Okay, stay calm. Where are you now?
Aim.
Pa?
Come out.
I won't hurt you, okay?
Pa.
Spread out and start looking.
They can't have gone very far.
Hey, sit down. Sit!
LOEI FORWARD GROUP
Go back and sit.
He hasn't woken up
I said sit down.
Mom didn't kill Sak, sis.
She almost did.
She didn't finish.
Nee.
Help…
Help me.
What are you, Phii Pong?
Eating a dead rat?
I'm not Pong. I wasn't.
Then why are you poking it with a stick?
Phii Pong has possessed you.
I'm not Phii Pong. I wasn't eating it.
Eat it!
Get off!
Eat it, Phii Pong!
Eat it!
Hey!
What?
Don't!
No!
Let me out!
Let me out! I'm not Pong!
Hey!
You remind me of Dad
when you make that face.
Why?
Do I disgust you?
I do get it.
I never wanted to be like this.
But once I started,
I couldn't stop myself.
It feels so good, you know,
getting rid of the scum.
What the hell?
It feels like I'm getting revenge
on that little shit.
Getting to choose who gets to live…
and who dies.
Why the hell did he keep this?
You know he didn't mean to.
But Uncle Sak was too damn smart, sis.
When he found out I'd done it again,
he took the body
and made it look like a Phii Pong attack
to trick the villagers.
He set himself up as a shaman,
making money off them.
What a piece of shit, right?
So Mom and Dad sent me off to Bangkok.
They said that the city would cure me.
But I was never gonna stop.
MOBILE MEDICAL VOLUNTEER UNIT
BO KLUEA, NAN
Hello there.
REGISTRATION
And once I became a doctor…
You can wait at the back, okay?
…it was even easier
to find more scum like them.
You're by yourself?
Yes, I'm alone.
MOBILE MEDICAL VOLUNTEER UNIT
Getting to choose who gets to live
and who dies.
All these scum
are all the fucking same.
Just different faces.
Every single tooth
that I pulled from their bodies…
was a reward I gave to myself.
And did you know,
they didn't plan to send me
to Bangkok alone.
You were supposed to go, too.
But Uncle Sak…
blackmailed us all about what I was doing.
Dad had to give him the money,
the land, everything.
But it was never enough.
Then he killed that kid named Mued…
…and used his teeth
to blackmail our family for more money.
But you have revenge.
So thank me.
These secrets are all yours.
But what do you want from me right now?
Well…
Mom would never say anything.
And Dad,
he's got one more chance
to protect his family.
So that leaves you.
I won't tell anyone.
Promise, I won't.
I won't say anything. Honestly.
I swear.
I'm not lying, Wat.
They all say that
when they're about to die.
Why should I believe you?
Hey!
Narong, where's your grandson?
- Hey, hey, uncle.
- Uncle!
- Uncle! No, no, no.
- Uncle! Uncle!
- Come back here.
What the fuck are you doing, huh?
Take him.
Inspector.
You find them?
No sign of the kid, sir.
Do you wanna die?
If you're gonna shoot me, just shoot!
Have you called for the boat yet?
It's on the way, Inspector.
Pull the trigger.
Come on. Do it!
I'm not afraid to die. Just do it!
Shoot!
Rescue! What's your ETA?
- Hurry up!
Come on. Come on!
CHIANG KHAN RESCUE UNIT
Aim.
Ms. Wan, please try to stay calm.
- Please just stay calm.
- My son. Where is he?
Just relax.
Your son is okay.
The nurse will bring him in shortly.
Don't worry.
MRS. WANRUDEE KUDPRATHUM
Do you remember how you got on that boat
at all?
Mm.
I blacked out.
I don't remember at all.
You and your son had Midazolam
in your blood.
It's an anesthetic.
It causes temporary memory loss
after injection.
You maybe dizzy and disoriented,
it's normal.
But do you really not remember?
Who were you talking to
right before you passed out?
Mom tried to protect her son.
Like you would.
You'd do anything for Aim.
If you had cared that day and helped me,
maybe I wouldn't be like this.
Who knows?
Sis, help me!
Help me, sis.
Help me, Wan!
Wan!
I told you to eat it!
Wan.
Help me, Wan!
Wan!
Go on. Eat it.
Whatever. It was a long time ago.
But right now,
for once, try acting like my sister.
Be still!
I didn't see anything.
Okay.
INVESTIGATION DIVISION
You killed your son-in-law, didn't you?
Tell me why you did it.
But he hurt my daughter.
I had to save her.
What about the Phii Pong murders?
Are you also behind them?
Sir! Sir! Excuse me, sir.
Please, sir, tell us the situation.
Uh, for now, we're bringing in
all units that are nearby here
to pursue every possible lead
on this killer.
But we admit that
serial killer cases in this country
are not common.
And I would like to, um, reassure everyone
that we're doing
everything we can right now.
Have you got any suspects yet?
- Do you have any suspects?
- Yeah.
- Tell us.
- Any suspects?
Sergeant, what's going on? How's the kid?
He's still unconscious.
Give us a hand here.
Come on, give us a hand here, Lieutenant.
Gentle. Easy, easy. All right.
CHIANG KHAN RESCUE UNIT
Inspector.
Here's the records.
Every province Dr. Wat lived in
matches the crime scenes.
If it wasn't the cops,
it was the shaman around here.
Just repeating the same thing for years
while nobody bothered to look
for the person who killed my son.
Back then, how do you remember him?
I don't.
You're all in it together, aren't you?
You're trying to take my land off me.
If a spirit wants you dead,
then you're dead anyway.
Doesn't matter how you die, Inspector.
Or maybe you're lying.
Which means I can't help him.
If you think it was my husband,
then arrest him.
Mom.
So do you have a suspect yet?
Yes, do you have any suspect?
Any suspects?
- The suspect, sir?
- Do you have a suspect or not?
- We have.
- Yeah? Who?
- Tell us more.
- Who is it?
We have to wait for our forensics team
to finish their work,
a lot of these cases are very old.
Can you at least tell us
if it was someone who lives local?
- Right.
- Yes, tell us.
Someone from around here?
- Is it a local?
- I can't answer that.
So let me reiterate.
Our officers are working
as hard as they all can, okay?
You can be certain of that, okay?
Thank you so much.
Sir, can you just answer
one more question?
THREE MONTHS LATER
What is it, huh?
The village chief asked me
to give you that.
For his son's ordination.
Come with me?
Think of it a farewell party
before you transfer back to Bangkok.
Mm.
How you doing?
Okay.
Now you're no longer a teacher,
what will you do?
Are you still investigating me, hmm?
I haven't really thought about it.
Taking him to school and other stuff
will fill all my time.
Terrible traffic in Bangkok.
Mmm.
And you?
Well, my place is far from the station.
The traffic will get to me, too.
Inspector…
I really appreciate you saving me.
If not for you,
anything could have happened.
I was just doing my job.
I wasn't saving you.
Hmm.
But you can't protect him forever.
Someone will find out.
Find out?
You know what I'm talking about.
- Please sit. Right.
- Hello.
Mm. Mm.
It's the price we agreed on
after deducting your debt, correct?
Pa.
Aim and I are moving to Bangkok.
This means I won't visit you,
not often.
Dad, so you must be well behaved.
Mmm.
I'm not mad at Mom and you
for what you did.
You believe that you're better than us,
Wan, but you're not.
Help me.
I'm leaving.
I'll come back to visit.
Please take care of your family.
Don't let anyone hurt us.
I sold the land.
It's all I could get, Mom.
You heard from your brother?
I'm leaving.
Don't you tell anyone
about what he did, okay?
He didn't mean to do it.
I think he's sick.
If you get in touch him, tell him…
to come and see me.
Ma.
Could you love me more?
Hmm?
As much as…
you love my brother, Mom?
I'm so sorry…
for letting you believe
that I love your brother more.
He, more than you, needed me.
I knew
that you could get by on your own.
Mom.
So we're moving far away.
Aren't you going to miss Grandpa,
Uncle Wat, and Grandma?
I probably will.
But I'll be fine.
I've got you.
NA SAO VILLAGE
NA SAO, CHIANG KHAN, LOEI